怎么了
What's up?
我又忘拿吉他了
I left my guitar here again.
好吧  没问题  好
Okay. No problem.  Okay.
好了  拿去吧
Okay. Here you go.
好  好
Okay.  Okay.
怎么了  你想一起玩点什么吗
What?  You want to hang out or something?
菲比  你来的不是时候
Phoebe. You caught me at a bad time.
你跟钱德勒...  没错
Are you and Chandler...?  Yes. Exactly.
好吧  要我帮你们伴奏吗  不必了
Okay. Do you guys want me to play for you?  No.
菲比  你好吗
Hey, Pheebs, what's up?
你问了一个引人深思的问题  钱德勒·宾
You ask an intriguing question, Chandler Bing.
天啊  你竟然请人帮你按摩
Oh, my God! You're getting a massage?
你从来不让我帮你按摩
You never let me massage you.
菲比  我可以解释
Phoebe, I can explain.
你说过你讨厌按摩
You told me you hate massages.
去买邮票  取干洗的衣服
Buy stamps. Pick up dry cleaning.
别让菲比进来
Don't let Phoebe in.
真不敢相信  你背着我这么做多久了
I can't believe this! How long has this been going on?
亚丽珊卓...
Well, Alexandra has...
她还有名字啊
It has a name?
菲比  别生气
Phoebe, don't get upset.
好吧  太迟了  我要走了
Okay. Oh, too late! I'm leaving.
来吧  钱德勒  我们走
Come on, Chandler, let's go.
我还是...
Well, I thought I'd...
好吧  管它呢
Yeah, what the hell.
《老友记》  第八季  第14集  神秘的储藏室
Friends S08E14 The One With The Secret Closet
好了  继续用力  加油
Oh okay, okay! One more push! One more push!
加油  亲爱的  就快生出来了
Come on honey, we're almost there! We're almost there!
乔伊  真高兴我们能在一起
Joey, I'm happy things worked out for us
我们就要有自己的孩子了
and we're having this baby together.
我如此爱你
I love you so much.
我也爱你
I love you too.
希望现在说这种话不会太煞风景...
I hope it's not an inappropriate time to say this...
你是我最棒的性伴侣
...you're the best sex I've ever had.
这种话随时都可以说
That's always appropriate.
来吧  继续用力  继续用力
Okay, come on, one more push. One more push.
好了
There we go.
你们的漂亮宝宝
Here is your beautiful baby.
恭喜
Congratulations.
希望你做爸爸比做朋友称职
I hope you're a better father than you are a friend!
乔伊  怎么了
Joey! Joey!  What?
发生了什么事  快来摸摸我的肚子
What's going on?  Come feel my belly.
这是宝宝第一次踢我
The baby's kicking for the first time.
你过来摸摸嘛
Will you please come feel this?
真的吗  对
Really?  Yes.
要不还是你...
You know what? Maybe you...
还是你过来吧  我没穿裤子
Maybe you should come to me. I'm not wearing any bottoms.
天啊
Oh, my God.
太不可思议了
It's unbelievable!
她踢得好用力  她就像是...
Wow, she is kicking so much. She's like...
那个讨厌的女足球员是谁来着
Who's that kind of annoying girl soccer player?
米亚·汉姆  米亚·汉姆
Mia Hamm?  Mia Hamm!
太神奇了  一只手抓好床单  乔伊
It's amazing.  One hand on the sheet, Joe.
抱歉
Sorry.
宝贝  亲爱的
Hey, babe.  Hey, honey.
刚收到巴伯跟菲伊宾送我们的结婚礼物
We got a wedding gift from Bob and Faye Bing.
他们不喜欢我们  对吧
They don't like us, do they?
谁说买不到六块以下的高级酒碗
Who says you can't get a nice punch bowl for under $6?
我们可以退回去
Maybe we can take it back.
上面都没写地址  怎么知道要退到哪里去
No, it doesn't say where it came from. Where would we return it?
何不从阳台把它丢到街上
How about to the street, from the balcony?
还是找个地方摆着吧
Why don't we just find a place for it?
放在那个储藏室里怎样
How about that cabinet?
那是放罐头食物的
No. That's for canned goods.
你忘了每样东西都要放在固定位置吗
Have you forgotten everything you learned at orientation?
那浴室旁边的储藏室呢
How about the closet by the bathroom?
让我来吧  不  我来就行了
Okay. Let me do it.  No, I'll do it.
亲爱的  你得学会放手
Honey, you have to learn to sit down and relax
偶尔把事情交给我来做
and let your husband take care of things once and awhile.
上锁了  你得帮帮我
It's locked. You have to help me.
为什么上锁了
Why is it locked?
没有为什么  我把私人物品放在那里
No reason. I keep private things in there.
我在这里住了一阵子了
I've been here a while,
从没见过里面放的是什么东西
and I've never seen what's inside that closet.
里面到底放了什么
What is in there?
女性用品
Feminine stuff.
你别以为说是女性用品就能唬住我
Don't try to make me uncomfortable with feminine stuff!
钱德勒  那里面没有你喜欢的东西
Chandler, there is nothing in there that concerns you!
你要是爱我  就忘了这件事吧
If you love me, you'll just let it go.
好吧  谢谢
Fine.  Thank you.
爱你
Love you.
钱德勒  今天天气真好啊
Hello, Chandler. Lovely day, huh?
那谁
You.
如果这话有帮助的话
Phoebe, if it helps,
亚丽珊卓只帮她做了三年按摩
Alexandra's only been massaging Monica for three years.
我说如果有帮助的话
If! I said, if it helps.
你为什么不让我帮你按摩
Why won't you let me massage you?
我会觉得尴尬
I mean I'd just... I'd be selfconscious.
你是我朋友  我得脱光衣服
You're my friend. I'd be naked.
莫妮卡  我们住在一起那么多年
Monica, we lived together for years.
我看过你没穿衣服的样子
I've seen you naked.
那不一样  我们当时是室友
That's different. We were roommates.
你什么时候见过
And when?
我对人体很好奇
I'm curious about the human body.
菲比  你肯定明白我为什么会觉得别扭
Come on, Phoebe. You can understand why this would be weird for me.
我是职业按摩师  技术一流
I'm a professional and I'm really good.
如果你觉得不舒服  我就住手
If you're uncomfortable, we can stop.
给我一个机会  拜托
Just give me a chance. Please? Okay?
好吧  如果你这么看重这点的话
Okay. If it means that much to you.
没错
It does.
如果你没法分享你的厨艺  你会有什么感觉
How would you feel if you couldn't share your cooking?
如果罗斯不能教我们
Or imaging how Ross would feel
龙的知识他会有什么感觉
if he couldn't teach us about dragons.
是恐龙  有什么区别
Dinosaurs.  Potato, potahto.
罗斯  宝宝会动了
Ross, the baby's kicking.
什么  是吗
What? It is?
她现在没在踢我
It's not kicking right now.
不过我们倒是很想看你再摘一次手套
Although we would love to see you do that again.
她什么时候动的  怎么回事
When? When was it kicking? What happened?
昨晚我感觉到了  就跑到乔伊房间
Last night. I just felt it and I went into Joey's room,
他在睡觉  但是没做梦
and he was sleeping.  A dreamless sleep.
天啊  宝宝会动了  真是太棒了
My God, the baby's kicking. That's great.
不过我希望宝宝第一次胎动的时候
Although I kind of wish I would have been there to feel
我能陪在你身边
the kicking for the first time.
如果你真的想摸  我的肚子正在咕咕叫呢
I got some stuff going on if you want to feel.
我不想再错过宝宝的一举一动了
Look, I don't want to miss any more baby stuff.
这是我的新传呼号码
So here's my pager number, okay?
只要发生跟宝宝有关的事立刻通知我
Anytime anything pregnancyrelated happens, use it.
我随时恭候  凌晨三点也无所谓
I'll be there. I don't care if it's three in the morning,
哪怕你只是想吃冰淇淋
and all you want is ice cream.
我能抄一份吗
Can I get a copy of that?
你裹上床单吗  对
Are you under the sheet?  Yes.
好了  我们开始吧
Great, let's begin.
力道还可以吧
How's the pressure?
很不错  菲比  你确实很厉害
It's nice. Wow, Phoebe, you are good.
这是明摆着的事  不过还是谢谢夸奖
Stating the obvious, but thank you.
一点都不奇怪  对吧  没错
And it's not weird, is it?  No.
没错  好好享受吧
That's right, you just enjoy.
爽
Oh, yeah!
爽啊  好吧
Oh, yeah!  Okay.
天啊  菲比
Oh, God, Phoebe!
就这样  就是那里
That's it! That's it, right there!
我没想打开你的储藏室
I wasn't trying to open your closet.
我发誓  我没想打开你的储藏室
I wasn't trying to open your closet, I swear.
莫妮卡管你很严  对吧
Monica runs a pretty tight ship here, doesn't she?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
莫妮卡有个秘密储藏室  她不肯让我看
Monica has a secret closet. She won't let me see what's in it.
为什么  我不知道
Why not?  I don't know!
她能有什么要藏着不让我看的
What could she possibly be hiding in here that I can't see?!
我不知道
I don't know.
我敢说是理查德
I bet it's Richard.
她为什么要把理查德关在里面
Why would Monica be keeping Richard in here?
我的第一反应是
Off the top of my head...
或者她想鱼与熊掌兼得
...maybe she's having her cake and eating it too.
你是"熊掌"  理查德只是"鱼"
You being the "cake," Richard being the "too."
或是...  又来了
Or...  And here we go.
我看过一部电影里有一扇门
I saw this movie once where there was a door
没有人知道里面藏了什么
Nobody knew what was behind it.
最后他们把门打开之后
When they finally got it open,
数以百万只虫子蜂拥而出
millions and millions and millions of bugs came pouring out
以人肉为食
and they feasted on human flesh.
尊重你老婆的隐私要不了你的命
It wouldn't kill you to respect your wife's privacy!
满是虫子的破储藏室
Stupid closet full of bugs!
乔伊  我感觉怪怪的  不太对头
Joey. Joey, something feels weird and not good weird.
我不...
I don't...
别担心  没事
Do not worry, ok?
我妹妹怀孕的时候
When my sisters were pregnant...
她们有各种奇怪的感觉
they got every weird feeling in the book,
结果根本没事
and it was always nothing.
真的吗  没错
Really?  Absolutely.
但我们得到医院检查一下  确保没事
But we'll stop by the hospital just to be sure.
我在路上呼罗斯  好
I'll page Ross on the way.  Okay. God!
瑞秋  看着我
Okay Rach, Rach, Rach look at me, look at me,
一切都会没事的  相信我
everything's gonna be fine, trust me. Okay.
来  握着我的手  我们走吧
Come on. Take my hand. Here we go.
我快骨折了
Crushing bones!
还好我们是要去医院
Good thing we're going to a hospital.
怎么样  她没事
So?  She's fine.
她出现了假性子宫收缩
She's experiencing BraxtonHicks contractions,
引起了子宫壁的轻度不适
mild discomfort caused by contractions in the uterine wall.
轻度不适
Mild discomfort?
这么说你也出现过假性宫缩喽
So I take it you've had one of these Braxton thingies?
一切都正常吗  对
But everything's normal?  Absolutely.
她和宝宝都没有危险  对
And there's no danger to her or the baby?  No.
如果不明情况  宫缩会引起不安情绪
Contractions can be unnerving if you don't know what they are,
但她没事
but she's fine.
谢谢你  医生
Thank you, doctor.
谢谢你这么好心冷静
And thank you for being nice and calm.
我一点都不冷静
Calm? I wasn't calm!
我从来没有这么害怕过
I've never been more scared in my entire life.
你说一切都会没事的
But wait you said everything was gonna be okay.
我知道什么  我又不是医生
What do I know? I'm not a doctor.
但一切都没事  我很好啊  你确定
But everything is okay. I'm fine.  You sure?
对  我真希望那个医生的子宫也会收缩
Yes. I got half a mind to contract that doctor's uterus though.
轻度不适  他没经历过  有什么资格发言
Mild discomfort! What's he talking about?
你没事吧  没事
Is everything okay?  Yes, everything's fine.
你呼我说"赶到医院来"  发生了什么事
Your page said, "Come to the hospital." What happened?
她出现了假性子宫收缩
Something called Braxton Hicks contraction.
那没什么大不了的
Thank god. That's no big deal.
很多女人都不会有感觉
Most women don't feel them.
没有子宫就没有发言权
No uterus, no opinion.
你买糖果干嘛  你呼我的时候
What's with the candy?  When you beeped me,
我正在电影院买零食
I was at the concession stand at the movie theater.
你自己去看电影吗  蒙娜
You went to the movies by yourself?  Mona!
我得回检查室去
I gotta go back in there.
发生了什么事
Why? What's wrong?
没事  我只是得回去...
No, everything's fine. I just gotta go back...
不  告诉我  怎么了
No, really, tell me. What's up?
我把内裤落在里面了
Look, I forgot my underwear.
谢谢你送她来医院
Thanks so much for bringing her to the hospital.
别放在心上  没有什么大不了
Don't worry about it. No big deal.
但应该由我送她来  我毕竟是孩子他爸
But still, it should have been me. I'm the dad.
如果还有疑问
If you have any questions,
这是假性宫缩的资料  谢谢
Here's information on Braxton Hicks.  Thanks.
对了  你送她过来是对的
By the way, you did the right thing by bringing her in.
你会是个好爸爸
You'll make a wonderful father.
我没有这家伙厉害  他买了糖果
Hey, not as good as this guy. He brought Twizzlers.
一定会有办法
There has got to be a way.
别紧张  寇克船长
Easy there, Captain Kirk.
你有发夹吗  有
Do you have a bobby pin?  Yeah.
不对  我不是九岁的小女孩
Oh, no, wait. I'm not a 9yearold girl.
那为什么你投球的时候很像
Then why do you throw like one?
或许莫妮卡有发夹
Maybe Monica has a bobby pin.
是啊  "莫妮卡"什么都有
Oh, sure, "Monica."
你暗恋瑞秋那事怎么样了
So, how's the hideously inappropriate crush on Rachel coming?
很不错  我该随时做好自杀的准备
Really good. I should be ready to kill myself any day now.
你这么快就找到了
Well, you sure found that quick.
我真希望对瑞秋的感觉能淡去
I wish I didn't feel this way about Rachel any more.
我希望一切能恢复正常
I wish things could go back to normal.
我喜欢跟她一起住
I love living with her,
在怀孕期间照顾她感觉也很棒
and helping out with the baby is amazing.
但罗斯会觉得自己像个局外人
But now I think Ross feels left out.
我送瑞秋去医院
When I took Rachel to the hospital,
医生还以为我是孩子他爸
the doctor thought I was the father.
罗斯的表情很不自然
You should have seen the look on Ross' face.
我不知道自己在干嘛
By the way, I have no idea what I'm doing here.
我只知道锁越捅越紧
For all I know, I'm just locking it more.
你试过用信用卡吗
Did you try opening it with a credit card?
好点子  好
That's a good idea.  Okay.
罗斯有点失落是吧
So Ross is kind of bummed, huh?
我感觉很过意不去  那不是你的错
I feel terrible.  It's not your fault.
不然你要怎么做  不送她去医院吗
What are you gonna do, not take her to the hospital?
你没做错事
You're doing nothing wrong.
但你不该爱上
Except for harboring an all consuming love
怀着他孩子的女人
for the woman whose carrying his baby.
理查德  如果你在里面
Richard, if you're in there,
麻烦把信用卡递给我
could you pass me my credit card?
你昨天的技术真的很棒
I gotta tell you, yesterday was amazing.
按摩感觉舒服极了
That massage felt so good.
我懂的
No, I got that.
你能每星期帮我按摩一次吗
So, what do you say we make it a weekly appointment?
好吧
Okay.
但你得知道  我的时薪涨到两百块了
You should know though, I've raised my rates to $200 an hour.
好吧  我是说五百块
Okay.  I mean 500.
什么  六百块
What?  600.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我给你按摩你的时候  你会发出叫床声
You make sex noises when you get massaged.
什么  我一下子就乱了手脚
What?  Yeah, and it really freaked me out!
之后我想用力弄痛你
And after a while I even tried to hurt you
结果你叫得更大声
and it just spurred you on.
你疯了吧
What? You're crazy.
我的叫声一点都不淫荡
There's nothing sexual about the noises I make.
是吗  这样一点都不淫荡吗
Really? There's nothing sexual about this?
天啊
Oh, God!
你看什么看
What are you looking at?
我是说  嗨
I mean, hi.
这简直太丢脸了
This is so embarrassing.
我再也不按摩了
Oh, my god. I'm never getting a massage again.
别让这个问题害你放弃按摩
No, you can't let this stop you from getting massages.
我有很多客人
Look, I have lots of clients
也会发出那种叫声
that make the same noises as you do.
真的吗  他们不是客人  是床伴
Really?  Well, not clients. Lovers.
我们再试一次
We'll try it again.
再来找我  我们想办法解决
Come back, and we'll work through it.
你确定  对
You sure?  Yes.
好吧  太棒了  失陪一下
I guess.  Great! Now, if you'll just excuse me.
你刚才听到你中意的声音了吗
So did you hear something you liked?
罗斯  你看  我学到了新把戏
Hey, Ross, check it out! I learned a new trick.
我帮你买了午餐
Hey, I brought you some lunch.
你真的太贴心了  美味啊
Oh, that's so sweet of you. Oh, yum.
你放了腌黄瓜吗  对
Did you put pickles on this?  Well, yeah.
怎么  瑞秋  怎么了
What? What? Rach, what?
发生了什么事
What's going on?
我帮她带了最爱吃的腌黄瓜金枪鱼三明治
I made her favorite, tuna salad with pickles.
腌黄瓜  那会让她恶心
Pickle? Pickle makes her sick.
让她吃腌黄瓜就像让我吃沙拉
Giving her pickle is like giving me salad.
抱歉  我不知道  你还好吗
I'm sorry Rach, I didn't know. Are you gonna be okay?
我没事
Yeah, I'll be fine,
趁我不在  谁能赶紧把那个三明治
But could someone please make sure that sandwich is gone
给解决掉  我在吃了
when I get out there?  I'm on it!
怎么会这样
I can't believe this.
我不该惹她恶心的
I shouldn't be the one making her throw up.
放轻松  罗斯  谁都可能做出这种事
Relax, Ross. It could happen to anyone.
你就不会  因为你了解她
Yeah, not to you. 'Cause you know this stuff.
我什么都不知道  亏我还是孩子他爸
I don't know any of it and I'm the father.
真希望自己能更多地参与其中
I wish I could be more involved, you know?
谁帮我记下来
Well, if anyone is keeping score,
我绝不会再吃金枪鱼了
I no longer eat tuna.
我能跟你们谈一谈吗
Can I talk to you guys for a second?
可以啊  怎么了
Yeah.  What's up?
坐吧  我想谈谈我们现在的情况
Sit down. I wanna talk about our situation.
你要跟我们分手吗
Are you breaking up with us?
我想说的是...
The thing is...
因为我跟瑞秋一起住  我参与了不少事情
...because I live with Rachel, I'm here for a lot of stuff.
而罗斯却不断错过  所以
And Ross is missing everything. So...
怎么了
Yeah?
也许你们两个应该住在一起
Maybe you two should live together.
你要我搬出去吗  你不想让我住在这里了
Are you asking me to move out? You don't want me here?
不是  我喜欢跟你一起住  只不过...
No, I love living with you. It just seems that...
要找室友  也最好是孩子他爸
...if you're gonna have a roommate, it may as well be the father.
乔伊  我觉得罗斯不希望
But, Joey, I don't think Ross wants me to move into his apartment
我搬过去干扰他的生活
and disrupt his life like that.
或许他希望我搬过去
Or he does.
我很乐意照顾你跟宝宝
I would love to be around for you and the baby.
我们可以先试一阵子
We can just try it, like on a temporary basis.
但咱们有太多过往
But Ross, it's you and me.
对  但我们不会有感情牵扯
Sure, but it wouldn't be anything romantic.
我在和蒙娜交往  该死  又把蒙娜忘了
I'm dating Mona. Damn it, Mona!
我跟她约好一小时前见面
I was supposed to meet her an hour ago.
我这是怎么了
What is wrong with me?
你们意下如何
So, what do you think?
我不知道  那很疯狂吧  不
I don't know. Is it crazy?  No, no, it's not...
乔伊  这是个聪明点子
Joey, this is a smart idea.
我早该想到的
Well, I was due.
就这么办吧  我搬过去
Okay, let's do it. I'll move in.
真的吗  对
Really?  Yeah.
瑞秋  那真是太棒了
Rach, that's great. That's great.
还不赖嘛  我自己就把这玩意卸下来了
Not too shabby. I got this all off myself...
用我老婆的工具
...using my wife's tools.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你是怎么把它打开的
How did you get in there?
你很邋遢
You're messy.
不  你不该看到这个场面的
No! You weren't supposed to see this!
我娶了弗雷德·山福德（垃圾场主）
I married Fred Sanford.
钱德勒  你不了解
No, Chandler, you don't understand.
好吧  现在你知道了
Okay, okay, fine! Now you know, okay?
我很病态  不  老婆  你不病态
I'm sick.  No, honey, you're not sick.
我爱你不是因为你井井有条
Look, I don't love you because you're organized.
不论如何  我都爱你
I love you in spite of that.
真的吗
Really?
你发誓不会告诉任何人  对
Promise you won't tell anyone?  Yes.
既然我知道了  那如果我有多余的东西
And look, now that I know if I got some extra stuff lying around,
可以也放进那个储藏室吗
can we share the closet?
可是...
Well... It's just...
我怕你会把里面弄乱
I'm afraid you might mess it up.
瑞秋彻底搬出去了  你还好吧
So Rachel's all moved out? How you taking it?
我本想喝几瓶啤酒  但我把啤酒都丢了
I wanted to have a few beers, but I got rid of those
因为瑞秋受不了那个味道
because Rachel couldn't stand the smell of them.
我买了不少加钙的柳橙汁
I have thrown back a lot of orange juice with calcium.
已经过期几星期了
It's a couple weeks past its expiration date,
所以会有点酒精的效力
so it's got a bit of a kick.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
开什么玩笑  我棒极了
You kidding me? Yeah, I'm great.
我好到不能再好  我很好
I'm better than great. I am good.
现在她搬走了
Now that she's gone,
我可以做以前不能做的事了
I can do stuff around here that I couldn't do before.
譬如...
Like...
我又能脱光衣服到处走了
I can walk around naked again.
我可以...
I can...
我可以在客厅看黄片
I can watch porn in the living room.
这对我来说是件好事
This is good for me.
我喜欢一个人过日子  我喜欢这个样子
I like being on my own. I'm better off this way.
我是一匹孤独的狼
I'm a lone wolf.
我是个孤单的硬汉
A loner. Alone.
永远都是一个人
All alone. Forever.
狼都哀嚎成这样了  怎么还没人给个拥抱呢
What's a wolf gotta do to get a hug around here?
好了  放轻松
That's it, just relax.
加油  再来  天啊
Come on, more.  Oh, God!
你喜欢那样  对吧
You like that, don't you?
对  就是那里
Yeah, right there.
你要吗  我这就给你  宝贝
Want it there? Take it there, baby.
菲比  对  喊我的名字  快点
Phoebe?  Yeah, say my name. Say it.
现在我要帮你盖上被子
And now I'm going to cover you back up.
我接下来几周不会再跟你说话了
And I won't be speaking with you for several weeks.